[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The film Young Frankenstein is a parody of the various film adaptations of the Frankenstein novel written by this novelist.", "correct_answer": "Mary Shelley", "incorrect_answers": ["R.L. Stine", "Stephen King", "Robin Cook"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1955 Science Fiction film, directed by Joseph M. Newman, concerns aliens arriving on Earth to get some assistance in fighting their war.", "correct_answer": "This Island Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["They Came as Zombies!", "Forbidden Planet", "The Isle of Dr. Moreau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of the following states will you not find the mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["Indiana", "Kentucky", "Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What cat breed, which originated in France, has thick waterproof grey fur, gold-colored eyes and large muscular body?", "correct_answer": "Chartreux", "incorrect_answers": ["Chausie", "Pixie-bob", "LaPerm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first member of The Monkees to quit, shortly after the bands Far East tour in December 1968?", "correct_answer": "Peter Tork", "incorrect_answers": ["Micky Dolenz", "Davy Jones", "Michael Nesmith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Dynasty star featured in the December, 1983 issue of Playboy magazine.", "correct_answer": "Joan Collins", "incorrect_answers": ["Heather Locklear", "Emma Samms", "Catherine Oxenberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first meal eaten on the moon?", "correct_answer": "Bacon, sugar cookies and peaches", "incorrect_answers": ["Tang, rib roast, peas and carrots, and sugar cookies", "Milk, eggs with cheese, and blueberries", "Tang, chicken breast, and ice cream"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the original story on which the movie Bambi is based?", "correct_answer": "Felix Salten", "incorrect_answers": ["Lance Rentzel", "Ken Anderson", "Carlo Collodi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People suffering from fibromyalgia may be genetically predisposed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Silas the Monk , the loyal servant of the Lord, repeated what phrase in the movie The Da Vinci Code?", "correct_answer": "I am a ghost", "incorrect_answers": ["I am nobody", "I am holy", "I am Silas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the closest point to the sun in the Earths orbit called?", "correct_answer": "Perihelion", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphelion", "Summer Solstice", "Autumnal Equinox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word \u201chippopotamus\u201d mean?", "correct_answer": "River horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Water pig", "Fat horse", "River pig"]}]